{
  "collection": "hira-basic",
  "name": "Hiragana",
  "subtitle": "ひらがな",
  "description": [
    "Hiragana (ひらがな) is one of two Japanese syllabaries and a basic component of the Japanese writing system. Each character represents a particular syllable, generally composed of a consonant and vowel sound (or just a vowel).",
    "The system is complicated by various modifiers and deprecated sounds, which will be found in the Advanced Hiragana collection once we code it."
  ],
  "hasAudio": true,
  "hasImages": true,
  "items": [
    {
      "id": "hira-あ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "あ",
      "back": "a"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-い",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "い",
      "back": "i"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-お",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "お",
      "back": "o"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-う",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "う",
      "back": "u"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-え",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "え",
      "back": "e"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-か",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "か",
      "back": "ka"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-き",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "き",
      "back": "ki"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-く",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "く",
      "back": "ku"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-け",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "け",
      "back": "ke"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-こ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "こ",
      "back": "ko"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-さ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "さ",
      "back": "sa"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-し",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "し",
      "back": "shi"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-す",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "す",
      "back": "su"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-せ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "せ",
      "back": "se"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-そ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "そ",
      "back": "so"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-た",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "た",
      "back": "ta"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ち",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ち",
      "back": "chi"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-つ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "つ",
      "back": "tsu"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-て",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "て",
      "back": "te"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-と",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "と",
      "back": "to"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-な",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "な",
      "back": "na"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-に",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "に",
      "back": "ni"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ぬ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ぬ",
      "back": "nu"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ね",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ね",
      "back": "ne"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-の",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "の",
      "back": "no"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-は",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "は",
      "back": "ha"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ひ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ひ",
      "back": "hi"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ふ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ふ",
      "back": "fu"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-へ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "へ",
      "back": "he"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ほ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ほ",
      "back": "ho"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ま",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ま",
      "back": "ma"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-み",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "み",
      "back": "mi"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-む",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "む",
      "back": "mu"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-め",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "め",
      "back": "me"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-も",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "も",
      "back": "mo"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ら",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ら",
      "back": "ra"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-り",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "り",
      "back": "ri"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-る",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "る",
      "back": "ru"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-れ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "れ",
      "back": "re"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ろ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ろ",
      "back": "ro"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-や",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "や",
      "back": "ya"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ゆ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ゆ",
      "back": "yu"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-よ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "よ",
      "back": "yo"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-わ",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "わ",
      "back": "wa"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-を",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "を",
      "back": "wo"
   },
   {
      "id": "hira-ん",
      "type": "hiragana",
      "front": "ん",
      "back": "n"
   }
  ]
}
